{
    "id": "3460733011c94efe82ba18b6ee49f0cc",
    "title": "Phrasal Verbs With Cut",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "afb36ccf17e349919d9e77983bce8a94",
            "title": "Phrasal Verbs With Cut",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "We need to cut ................................ on luxuries.",
                    "description": "To cut back on something is to reduce spending on it.",
                    "answers": [
                        "back",
                        "off",
                        "down"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "You need to cut .............................. on sugar. You are diabetic!",
                    "description": "To cut back on something is to reduce its consumption.",
                    "answers": [
                        "up",
                        "back",
                        "out"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Environmentalists are against the project because they do not want the government to cut .............................. trees to make room for a theme park.",
                    "description": "To cut down trees is to bring them down by cutting them.",
                    "answers": [
                        "up",
                        "off",
                        "down"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "If you want to lose weight, you should cut ............................ on your calorie intake.",
                    "description": "To cut down on something is to reduce the amount of something.",
                    "answers": [
                        "in",
                        "out",
                        "down"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "If my dad hadn't cut me ..................................., I would never have found a job.",
                    "description": "To cut someone off is to stop providing financial support to them.",
                    "answers": [
                        "up",
                        "out",
                        "off"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "That dunce cut me ................................ as I was about to conclude my presentation.",
                    "description": "To cut somebody off is to interrupt them as they speak. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "off",
                        "out",
                        "up"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Cut ................................ the lamp when you leave the room.",
                    "description": "To cut off an electrical device is to turn it off.",
                    "answers": [
                        "up",
                        "down",
                        "off"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "The health scare compelled him to cut ............................... smoking.",
                    "description": "To cut out smoking is to refrain from smoking.",
                    "answers": [
                        "up",
                        "down",
                        "out"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "The generator suddenly cut .................................. and the house plunged into darkness.",
                    "description": "When a device cuts out, it stops working.",
                    "answers": [
                        "off",
                        "out",
                        "up"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "We cut .................................... the woods and got home in less than an hour.",
                    "description": "To cut through something is to take a short cut through it.",
                    "answers": [
                        "in",
                        "across",
                        "through"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "He was badly cut ..................................... by his attackers.",
                    "description": "Cut up can mean wound.",
                    "answers": [
                        "off",
                        "up",
                        "down"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Critics cut .................................... the movie mercilessly.",
                    "description": "Cut up can mean criticize or censure.",
                    "answers": [
                        "down",
                        "up",
                        "in"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}